unblock-proxy.com 2008-12-21

# Privacy Policy - Unblock-Proxy.com

## Unblock Proxy

**Introduction**

1\. Thank-you for taking the time to review our Privacy Policy. At times, this site will hence forth be referred to as UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM will collect certain personal information about coustomers and visitors to websites hosted by us. Such information will include non-identifialbe personal information. Non-identifiable information is gathered automatically when you visit our website or those websites hosted by us, and stored for us in our system. 

2\. The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain to customers what type of information we will collect and how that information is used. In most cases, we collect this information to ensure network integrity and that we continue to provide you with the most relevant content and best possible service that suits your needs. In some cases, we are required by law to collect personal information about customers. Execpt where the law requires otherwise, we undertake to protect the confidentiality of such data. 

**Confidentiality**

3\. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM repects customer privacy and the privacy of those accessing our website, or those websites hosted by us. We undertake to protect the confidentiality of our customers and users. We undertake not to sell your personal information to third parties for commercial or maketing purposes. 

**Collection of Personal Data**

4\. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM collects personal data about our users when you visit a website hosted by us; and through the use of cookie technology. We may also combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from our bussiness partners or affiliates. 

**Use of Personal Data**

5\. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM may collect and share aggregated user data with bussiness partners, sponsors or other third parties for the purpose of developing content and ensuring relevant advertising and content, such user data will never be used to identify users. These business partners and affiliated companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 

6\. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM may log the websites you visit; collect IP addresses and information about your opertaing system and the type of browser you use for the purpose of network/system administration; to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. This data however will not be used to identify individual users who will at all times remain anonymous. 

7\. Any information UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM collects from you through correspodence with us, wheter via e-mail, telephonically or by written letter, will only be used to address the matters within that correspondence. If this requires such correspondence within IF or third party to ensure customer service, your personal information will only be disclosed to the point necessary to address your qurey or concerns, and will otherwise be kept confidential. 

**Public Space (Buttetin Boards, Chat Rooms and Third-Party Sites)**

8\. Any information that customers disclose in a public space, including on any bulletin board, chat room or any site UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM may host for you, is available to anyone else who visits that space. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM cannot safeguard any information you disclose there. 

**Site Linking**

9\. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM's website contain mainy links to sites that belong to third parties unrelated to us. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM cannot be held responsible for any use of your personal information arising from you disclosing personal information on third pary sites. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM cannot protect any information you may disclose on these sites and recommends that you review the privacy policy statements of those sites you vist. 

**General**

10\. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM reserves the right to disclose information about customers where required in good faith, to do so by law or to exercise our legal rights or defend ourselves against legal claims. 

11\. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM futher reservse the right to share information with law enforcement to investigate or prevent illegal activities being commited over our network. 

12\. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM further resrves our rights to disclose your personal information where you have given us explicit legal written consent to do so. 

13\. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM reserves the right to monitor user and network traffic for site security purposes and prevent any unauthorized attempts to tamper with our site or cause damage to our property. 

14\. UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy or update it without further notification. It may be necessary to from time to time, check UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM's privacy policy for changes. Customers and site visitors bear the responibility to ensure that they have read the changes. Customers and site visitors bear the responsibility to ensure that they have read the changes or updates as the case may be. 

Thank-you for having read our Privacy Policy

If you agree to the Privacy Policy please [**CLICK HERE**](http://www.new.unblock-proxy.com/) to go back to **UNBLOCK-PROXY.COM**

If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy please [ **CLICK HERE** ](http://www.freeproxylist.info/).
